(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T14:17:53.453237",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hello?
Is... anybody... there?...
It's so... dark...
No one gets it...
No one... understands.
I feel.... hunger...
I feel.... cold...
please...
Is...anybody...there?
Is... anybody... there?
Hello?
よおうな垂れてるその兄ちゃん
Hey mister who's hanging his head down,
何か辛いことあったんか？
did something tough happen to you?
俺で良けりゃ話してくんない？
If you don't mind, won't you talk to me?
力になるぜ
I'll help you out.
一体どんなことがあった？
What on earth could have happened?
それひっでえ話の兄弟
That's a brutal story, brother.
これをやっから元気出しいな
Take this and cheer up.
金ならまた今度でいいさ
You can pay me next time.
shanti shanti shanti shanti
happy happy happy candy
many many money
眠らない夜のチャイナタウン
Chinatown on a sleepless night,
その全てが縄張り
everything here is our territory.
老若男女問わずお客人
Guests of all ages and genders,
使い終わったら捨てりゃいいじゃん
once you're done using them, just throw them away.
今夜も来たのかい
Did you come again tonight?
お気に召したかい
Did it please you?
代金はこれくらい
The payment is about this much.
え？え？え？
Eh? Eh? Eh?
払えないのかい
Can't you pay?
ならばしょうがない
Then it can't be helped.
君にぴったりの仕事があるからこっちに付いてきな
There's a job perfect for you, so follow me this way!
こっちに付いてきな
Follow me this way!
耳を塞いだって ざわざわは聞こえてくる
Even if I plug my ears, the buzzing still reaches me
酸性雨で花は枯れた
The flowers died from acid rain
明日咲くはずの花は枯れた
The flowers that were supposed to bloom tomorrow died
意味のないことばかりだ
Everything is just meaningless
意味ばかり求めすぎるから
Because we keep asking for meaning too much
トンビは山に泣いた もう帰れないと泣いた
The black kite screamed in the mountains, crying that it can't return
掃き溜めみたいな憧れも 遠くから見惚れていた
Even my longing, which looked like a garbage dump, I used to admire
憧れが駆け込み乗車
Longing rushed onto the train
いたたまれなく頭を垂れた
And I hung my head in shame
絶望と君、隣り合わせ
Despair and you, side by side
自暴自棄とは背中合わせ
Desperation is right behind us
がらんどうが乗り合わせて 乗り過ごしたんだ幸福を
Emptiness boarded together and we missed out on our happiness
空洞 空洞
Empty hole, empty hole
誰もが野垂れ死んだって その頃には忘れるくせに
Even if we die by the roadside, we'll forget by that time anyway
「信じてる」も「愛してる」も
Even "I believe you" and "I love you"
オーナメント巻いてる 空洞 空洞
Are wrapped around as ornaments, empty hole, empty hole
何にもやる気が起きないよ
I don't have any motivation to do anything
やりたいことなんかないよ
There's nothing I want to do
反省なんかももうしないよ
I won't reflect on myself anymore
責任なんてもたないよ
I won't take any responsibility
別れた人はもう忘れた
I've already forgotten the people who left
でも忘れたこと忘れない
But I don't forget that I forgot them
亡霊と僕ら生きている つまりは憑りつかれてたんだ
We live with ghosts, in other words we were haunted
中二病
Chuunibyou...
大言壮語な妄想を抱き
those with grandiose delusions,
目立ちたい願望に憑りつかれ
those desperate to stand out,
自分には隠された知識や秘められた力があると確信する者たち
and who have convinced themselves that they have hidden knowledge or secret powers.
私、感じる、体中に
I... feel it, it's in my veins.
頭が、頭が、響く
my... head, my head keeps pounding...
何かが私を呼んでいる
something is calling me
「お前は誰だ？」
"who are you?"
もし闇が招くなら
if the darkness beckons
じゃあ誰が私を止めるの
then who's to stop me
Consentes Dei / Juno / Jupiter / Minerva / Apollo / Mars / Ceres / Mercurius / Diana / Bacchus / Vulcanus / Pluto / Vesta / Venus
微睡みの淵で目蓋に揺蕩う
In the deep depths of my light nap, my eyes are shaking while closed
夢想の神は優雅に微笑み死を降し
The god of dreams smiles elegantly as he issues death to us all
時空を総べる因果の鎖は絡み出す
The chains of all the corpses control space and time as they start to tangle
神の与えし空想 Program
The god above created a fantasy program
さあ eins zwei drei! 重なり合う
So now, eins zwei drei! Together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 死を躱して
So now, eins zwei drei! Until the game is done
滅亡の遊戯に焦がれる奇跡を奪う Survivalgame
I'll grab the miracle in front of me within a survival game
螺旋のように
Or we'll be out of control
Consentes Dei / Juno / Jupiter / Minerva / Apollo / Mars / Ceres / Mercurius / Diana / Bacchus / Vulcanus / Pluto / Vesta / Venus
泡沫の未来
Trying very hard to rewrite our now close ending futures
書き換えるように
The noises of rebirth that connect fantasies together, begins to resound
空想結ぶ輪廻のノイズが鳴り渡る
Time is twisting and the laws of destiny start crumbling away
時間は歪み因果の旋律は崩れ去る
The god above created a succession program
神の与えし継承 Program
So now, eins zwei drei! Together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 連なり合う
So now, eins zwei three! Away from death, we'll run
Consent es dei, Juno, Jupiter, Minerva...
微睡みの淵で目蓋に揺蕩う
In the deep depths of my light nap, my eyes are shaking while closed
夢想の神は優雅に微笑み死を降す
The god of dreams smiles elegantly as he issues death to us all
時空を総べる因果の鎖は絡み出す
The chains of karma control space and time as they start to tangle
神の与えし空想 Program
The god above created a fantasy program
さあ eins zwei drei! 重なり合う
So now, eins zwei drei! together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 死を躱して
So now, eins zwei drei! until the game is done
消滅の遊戯に焦がれる奇跡を奪う Survivalgame
I'll grab the miracle in front of me within the survival game
螺旋のように
Like a spiral...
神の与えし継承 Program
The god above created a succession program
さあ eins zwei drei! 貫なり合う
So now, eins zwei drei! together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 死を振り切って
So now, eins zwei drei! away from death, we'll run
消滅の遊戯に抗う奇跡に挑む Erasergame
I'll test the miracle by facing the eraser game
さあ eins zwei drei! 重なり合う
So now, eins zwei drei! together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 死を躱して
So now, eins zwei drei! until the game is done
泡末の未来書き換えるように
Trying very hard to rewrite our now close ending futures
空想繋ぐ輪音のノイズが鳴り渡る
The noises of rebirth that connect fantasies begin to resound
時間は歪み因果の規律は崩れ去る
Time is twisting and the laws of destiny start crumbling away
神の与えし継承 Program
The god above created a succession program
さあ eins zwei drei! 貫なり合う
So now, eins zwei drei! together we'll be one
さあ eins zwei drei! 死を振り切って
So now, eins zwei drei! away from death, we'll run
消滅の遊戯に抗う奇跡に挑む Erasergame
I'll test the miracle by facing the eraser game
無限のように
Like within a nightmare...
繋がる奇跡を歌う
Singing of the connected miracle
サバイバルゲーム
Survival game
螺旋のように
Like a spiral
哀れなる傍観者 焦がれる生死よりも遠く
The observers pitying us, are farther away than the death I yearn for
最果てにある箱庭にはで
In the little garden at the very end
終わりのかない奇跡があると 信じてた
Or so I believed, that an endless miracle exists
アンダー 譲歩すなら共犯者 ひとりぼっち 愛を戴冠
“Under” if you say innocent, you’re complicit and weak, I’m so lonesome, please love me
アンダー 何かが足りないんだ 求め合う決まり なんとかしたいフューチャー
“Under” my cord’s being pulled but nothing’s ever enough, contractual desires, oh what to do, future
馬鹿じゃん馬鹿じゃんね
You're so stupid, you're so stupid!
まだ痛いって痛いってさ出さないね
You're still saying it hurts, it hurts, refusing to let it out
アンダー 廻るクリーンゲーム
“Under” the revolving clean game
救えない ぬくもりのスティール
Stealing an un-rescuable warmth
馬鹿じゃん馬鹿じゃんね
You're so stupid, you're so stupid!
まだ好きって好きってさきついね
You're still saying you love me, it's so tough
どれがいらないの？
Which one of these do we not need?
許されないが走ったから
Because the unforgivable started running
あなたの基盤になったよ
It became your foundation
大一番のヒーロー選んだよ
I chose the ultimate hero
決闘を刻み込んだよ
And carved the duel into place
やめてなんてなんでなの？
Saying "stop", why, why is that?
止まらないだよ
It just won't stop!
裁きを下す代償女王が欲しい 欲しいの 次の夢をくれよ
The queen of judgment demands her price, I want it, give me my next dream!
隠したい 譲りたくないそう跳ね
Wanting to hide it, refusing to give it up, leaping like that
伴えない 踏めない信仰心
Incompatible, unyielding religious devotion
馬鹿じゃん馬鹿じゃんね
You're so stupid, you're so stupid!
街を覚えてない覚えてない 鈍いね
Not remembering the town, not remembering at all, how dull
使えない 記憶の監獄で揺れてたい
Useless, wanting to sway in the prison of memories
笑っちゃう 正義
Laughable justice
馬鹿じゃん馬鹿じゃんね
You're so stupid, you're so stupid!
ドアをノックして泣いたって
Knocking on the door and crying
だからあたしの理由になってよ 許さないだけ選んだよ
So become my reason, I only chose what I couldn't forgive
同情はせず突いてよ 悪を悪と憎んでよ
Don't sympathize, just pierce through, detest evil as evil
止まらないだよ
It just won't stop!
裁きを下す代償女王が欲しい 欲しいの 次の夢をくれよ
The queen of judgment demands her price, I want it, give me my next dream!
アンダー アンダー
Under, under...
溶かしたい 求めてた正義に潰したい 汚れた未来を
Wanting to melt it, crush the justice I sought, the tainted future
馬鹿じゃん馬鹿じゃんね 頼ってよほら
You're so stupid, you're so stupid, rely on me, look
あなたの基盤になったよ 最後のヒーロー選んだよ 覚悟を刻み込んだよ
It became your foundation, I chose the final hero, and carved the resolve
やめてなんてなんでなの？ 止まらないだよ
Saying "stop", why, why is that? It just won't stop!
裁きを下す代償女王が欲しい 欲しいの 次の夢をくれよ
The queen of judgment demands her price, I want it, give me my next dream!
欲しい 欲しいの 次の夢をくれよ
I want it, I want it, give me my next dream!
くだらない ゼロイチの監視中
Useless zero-one surveillance
壊れぬコツでさ 咲こうぜ
With unbreakable tips, let's bloom!
...I feel myself falling
into complete deafening darkness
A blanket of monochrome solitude...
there is no one
alone
you're not alone
I'm alone
I'm all alone
僕が
I am...
僕がついている
I am with you.
she is coming...
the time has come
to pack away all the joys
you don't want to hear my apology, get it off my chest
I would do my best
I know what you fear, similarities we possess
never will I pass the test
the scene is fading
can my soul be put to rest?
death is gonna come for me
be the change I couldn't be
can you find a life that's like fairy tales far from this tragedy?
sad you had to wait for me
feels like an eternity
please forgive me for my sins
angels wings lifting and setting me free
death is gonna come for me
be the change I couldn't be
can you find a life that's like fairy tales far from this tragedy?
sad you had to wait for me
feels like an eternity
please forgive me for my sins
angels wings lifting and setting me free
the question of my love, my love
slipping right through the cracks and crumbling to dust
このぬくもりはどこへ行くの
Where is this warmth heading?
明日になれば消えてしまうの
Will it disappear by tomorrow?
胸の鼓動を合わせたならば
If we align the beating of our hearts,
同じ深みへ降りてゆけるの
Can we descend into the same depths?
いつもいつも傍にいるよ どんな遠く
Always, always by your side, no matter how far away
君の心が迷っても
your heart may wander.
狩りの刃 この胸をさらして
Exposing this chest to the hunting blade...
抱きしめる
Holding me close...
ずっと…
Forever...
君は一人で どこへゆくの
Where are you going all alone?
振り返るのが 怖いくせに
Even though you're afraid to look back.
怖いだけなのに
Even though you're just scared.
胸の形も 悲しい色も
The shape of our hearts and our sad colors...
本当はきっと よく似てるのに
Are actually so much alike.
いつかきっと 還る場所を 二人 同じ儚さで見つめている
We gaze with the same fleetingness at the place we'll return to.
この闇の中で どんなに離れていても
No matter how far apart we are in this darkness,
心は何より強い 絆で呼び合って
our hearts call out with a bond stronger than anything.
寂しいときには 君は笑っていても 分かるよ 冷たい指を 涙で温めてあげたい
When you're lonely, even if you smile, I want to warm your cold fingers.
側にいる… ずっと…
I'm right by your side... forever...
If you see through and follow you'll be
If I can be here with you, in the whole universe with you...
All I see through you is love, you'll be...
暗闇の中に二人でさまよいながら
Wandering together within the darkness,
無邪気な小鳥のように 翼を寄せていた
pressing our wings close like innocent little birds.
寂しいときには 笑顔に隠れる君は
When you're lonely, hiding behind a smile,
溶けない氷の刃 この胸をさらして
exposing your chest to the unmelting blade of ice...
抱きしめる ずっと…
Holding me close... forever...
側にいる ずっと…
By your side... forever...
If you see through and follow you'll be...
If I can be here with you, in the whole universe with you...
All I see through you is love, you'll be...
If you...
Have you ever looked through rose colored glasses?
A touch of red in our black and grey world...
One of pain and misery... suffocating, loathing, despair!
僕らの世界を色眼鏡で見たことある？
Have you ever looked at our world through rose-colored glasses?
見てごらん きっと気づくでしょう
Take a look, I'm sure you'll notice.
こんなに素敵な色があったなんて
That there could be such a wonderful color.
赤く染めよう
Let's dye it red.
寂しさの中 一粒落ちただけ
In the midst of the silence, a single drop fell
広がる波紋に 波打つ井戸の底
Causing ripples to spread at the bottom of the well
ざわついた 私の心の 森を揺さぶる木枯らしよ
Winter wind that shakes the forest of my restless heart
今日を過ごしているものなら そのままで
If you are living through today, stay just as you are
誰もがこの森で 静かな声を聴いて 雑音に涙した
Everyone in this forest listened to a quiet voice and shed tears at the noise
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
ureramu ureramu ureramu oto
born is born is born is a sound
nimiunooto denzushi denzu sea denzu sea
into the sounds of the sea it sinks and sinks
ureramu ureramu ureramu oto
born is born is born is a sound
nimiunooto uroma uroma uroma uroma
blending with the sounds of the sea over and over
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
ureramu ureramu ureramu oto
born is born is born is a sound
nimiunooto denzushi denzu sea denzu sea
into the sounds of the sea it sinks and sinks
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
rurekute shieka woki to nakaya da oniro kokono shi tawa
ceaselessly and quietly forest this in sounds of cacophony the
tai tsuwazadekazushi teshisoku namae taha too ku meshihi nirimonoko
heart noisy my in peace restore
ureramu ureramu ureramu oto
born is born is born is a sound
nimiunooto denzushi denzu sea denzu sea
into the sounds of the sea it sinks and sinks
作詞：畑亜貴 作曲：神前暁
Lyrics: Aki Hata / Music: Satoru Kosaki
ひとり語りしてもいいですか
May I tell you my story?
カモメにそっと呟いた
I whispered softly to the seagulls.
女一途な真心のせて
With a woman's single-hearted devotion,
北の海風凍てついた
The northern sea breeze freezes to the bone.
はぐれ恋散る 怨み節さえ
Even the grudge blues of stray, scattered love...
遠いあんたにゃ届かない
...cannot reach distant you.
佇んで泣き濡れて三十路岬
Standing, weeping and soaked at Misoji Cape.
ふたりだけの宿で泣き崩れ
Collapsing in tears at the inn we shared alone,
愛した夜を悔やんでも
Even if I regret the night we loved—
男勝りな約束ばかり 何も叶えず終わります
All those boastful promises ended without fulfilling a thing.
波の飛沫にこの身投けたら
If I cast this body into the ocean spray,
遠いあんたに逢えそうて
I feel like I could meet you again.
恋しさに捧げたい三十路魂
I want to dedicate this thirty-year soul to my longing.
みつどめいの泡と知りもせず
Without knowing it was just a fleeting bubble,
愛した罪は消えないの
The sin of loving you will never fade.
誰を選ぶか決められないと
Saying you couldn't decide who to choose,
別れ上手なひとてした
You were always so good at leaving.
はぐれ恋散る 怨み節さえ
Even the grudge blues of stray, scattered love...
中二病って何だ...
What is chuunibyou...?
ずっと探してた答えは一体何なんだ。
What on earth is the answer I've been searching for?
今までたどり着いた答えが納得できぬ。
I cannot accept the answers I've reached until now.
ならば、自分で作るさ！
If that's the case, then I'll make my own!
本当の中二病は... そう... すべては...
The true meaning of chuunibyou... that's right... everything is...
魂だ！！！！！！
THE SOUL!
めざめよ！！！マイソウル！！
AWAKEN! MY SOUL!!
踏み込むぜ アクセル
Step on the accelerator,
駈け引きは無いさ そうだろう
There's no bargaining, right?
夜をぬけろ
Slip through the night.
ねじ込むさ 最後に
Shove it in at the very end,
差し引き ゼロさ そうだろう
The net balance is zero, right?
日々を削る
Chipping away at the days.
心を そっと 開いて
Open your heart gently,
ぎゅっと 引き寄せたら
And pull it in tight.
届くよ きっと 伝わるよ もっと
It'll reach you, I'm sure it'll convey more.
さあ
Come on,
生き急いで 搾り取って
living in a rush, squeezing it out,
綻びる足だけど前よりずっとそう、遠くへ
with frayed legs, but heading far, far further!
心を そっと
Open your heart gently,
開いて ぎゅっと 引き寄せたら
and pull it close...
届くよ きっと 伝わるよ もっと
It'll reach you, I'm sure it'll convey more.
届くよ きっと
It'll reach you for sure,
伝うよ もっとさあ
it'll resonate even more, come on!
生き急いで 搾り取って
Living in a rush, squeezing it out!
綻びる 足だけど
With frayed legs,
前より ずっと そう 遠くへ
heading far, far further than before!
奪い取って 掴んだって
Snatching it away and grabbing hold,
君じゃないなら 意味はないのさ
If it's not you, it has no meaning.
だから もっと もっと もっと 遥か彼方
So even further, further, further into the distance!
踏み込むぜ アクセル
Step on the accelerator,
駈け引きは無いさ そうだろう
There's no bargaining, right?
夜をぬけろ
Slip through the night.
ねじ込むさ 最後に
Shove it in at the very end,
差し引き ゼロさ そうだろう
The net balance is zero, right?
日々を削る
Chipping away at the days.
心を そっと 開いて
Open your heart gently,
ぎゅっと 引き寄せたら
And pull it in tight.
届くよ きっと 伝わるよ もっと
It'll reach you, I'm sure it'll convey more.
心を そっと 開いて
Open your heart gently,
ぎゅっと 引き寄せたら
and pull it in tight.
届くよ きっと 伝わるよ もっと
It'll reach you, I'm sure it'll convey more.
届くよ きっと 伝うよ もっとさあ
It'll reach you, convey it more, come on!
生き急いで 搾り取って
Living in a rush, squeezing it out,
綻びる足だけど前よりずっとそう、遠くへ
with frayed legs, but heading far, far further!
奪い取って 掴んだって
Snatching it away and grabbing hold,
君じゃないなら 意味はないのさ
If it's not you, it has no meaning.
だから もっと もっと もっと 遥か彼方
So even further, further, further into the distance!
遥か彼方から
From far into the distance...
いつか歩く 扉に慣れた君の世界よ
Someday walking into your world accustomed to doors...
無理潰すのさ 白く
Crush it away in white!
足りねぇ！
Not enough!
全然足りねぇ！
Nowhere near enough!
I NEED MORE SOUL!
JUDGEMENT -審判- (Full Spec Edition)
[Song: JUDGEMENT - Shinpan - (Full Spec Edition)]
レールからはずれた 不良品の野犬さ
I'm a no-good stray dog off the rails,
だけど簡単には テールは振らないぜ
But I won't wag my tail so easily.
不良を日の野犬さ
A no-good stray dog...
だけど簡単には テールは振らないぜ
But I won't wag my tail so easily.
レールからはずれた 不良品の野良犬さ
Strayed from the rails, a defective stray dog
だけど簡単には テールは振らないぜ
But we don't wag our tails so easily
大人（イエスマン）に 成りそびれた
Failed to become a yes-man adult
若者（ワル）に残された 「No」という名の Justice
Left in the youth, Justice named "No"
Wow, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world 壊せ
Wow, Breakin' the law, breakin' the world, break it down
切り裂け Tenderness
Tear apart Tenderness
Wow, Breakin' the rule 六法全書じゃ縛れない 反乱分子さ
Wow, Breakin' the rule, can't be bound by the law, we're rebels
振り上げた握り拳が 俺達の JUDGEMENT
The clenched fist we raised is our JUDGEMENT
愛さえも知らない 不良品の野良犬さ
Not even knowing love, a defective stray dog
だけど地位や金じゃ 餌付けはできないぜ
But with status or money, you can't bribe us
傷ついて 傷ついて 全て失っちまっても
Hurt and hurt, even if we lose everything
染まっちゃならねぇ それこそが JUSTICE...
Won't be tainted, that's JUSTICE...
JUSTICE!
Wow, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world 壊せ
Wow, Breakin' the law, breakin' the world, break it down
切り裂け Tenderness
Tear apart Tenderness
Wow, Breakin' the rule お偉いさんじゃ懐かない 反乱分子さ
Wow, Breakin' the rule, won't bow to the big shots, we're rebels
振り上げろ握り拳を 俺達は そうさ俺達が JUDGEMENT...
Raise your clenched fist, we are... yes, we are JUDGEMENT...
JUDGEMENT...
チート gifted 荒業 wanted 禁忌 禁じ手 明らかな盲点 反則 異次元 この世の中のもんではないです
Cheat, gifted, foul play, wanted, taboo, forbidden move, obvious blind spot, otherworldly
無理ゲー それ聞いてないって...
Impossible game, you didn't tell me that...
Ay ライバル口を揃えては ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals all lining up, rivals all lining up
バグで、まぐれ、認めねぇぜってマジでこの世は全部生身で
Bugged, fluke, won't admit it, seriously, this world is all raw flesh!
It's raw It's raw yeah yeah yeah yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
実力を発揮し切る前に 相手の方がバックれてくらまし
Before showing full power, the opponent runs away and hides
愛が貰えるハードル very happy 相変わらず脱皮してる毎日
Hurdles where love is received, very happy, everyday shedding skin as usual
誰の七光りも要らない お前の ice より icy
Don't need anyone's borrowed light, icier than your ice
俺、パッと見出せない事ばっかりだけど very happy あ、切れてる…呆れてる周り
I only do things you wouldn't expect at first glance, but very happy, ah, snapping...
恵まれてる家族友達 もう反則的立ち位置 皆俺に任せとけば良い
Blessed with family and friends, already in an unfair position, just leave it to me
教科書に無い、問題集に無い 超BADな呪い listen
Not in textbooks, not in problem books, super BAD curse, listen
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best!
Mirror mirror on the wall, tell me, Who's the best? I'm the best!
Oh yeah 生身のまま行けるところまで
Oh yeah, going as far as raw flesh can take me
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
生身のまま行けるところまで To the next, To the 1番上
Going as far as raw flesh can take me, to the next, to the very top
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born To the next, To the 1番上
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born, to the next, to the very top
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Eyday, just staying as I am is super flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, nobody can interrupt
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Eyday, just staying as I am is super flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, nobody can interrupt
チート gifted 荒技 wanted
Cheated, gifted, beat and make 'em wanted
禁忌 禁じ手 明らかなり盲点
Taboo, forbidden move, obvious blind spot
反則 異次元 この世界の中のもんじゃないです
Foul play, another dimension, not of this world
無理ゲー それ聞いてないって
Impossible game, nobody told me that...
Ay ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, chasing my rival to the end,
Wow ライバル口を揃えて
Wow, chasing my rival to the end,
この生存自体が不可解な脳みそ
this survival itself is an inexplicable brain
ぶっ飛びまくりで気狂わない
flying high and going crazy
愛しグリーン・グリーン
loving green, green,
戦国学級ラス1ピン
Sengoku class, last 1 pin
この目が生み出す bling-bling
this eye produces bling-bling
パレット七万缶 関西なまり
palette of 70,000 cans, Kansai accent
生耳の言葉だ
raw words of speech,
音楽工学の恵み
blessed by music engineering
こよみままたばんぱん
calendar, every page bursting
漫画みたいに枯れても
even if withered like a manga,
まみれで張り合ってしまってる漫画
competing and getting covered in it
圧倒的地下から どんな底力
from the overwhelming underground, what hidden power
この言葉達は 入ってない
these words haven't entered yet,
この蔓に傷もついてない
no scars on this vine either
繰り返しらかしてだまっちがいて
repeating and deceiving, staying silent
がいにニュウ貴様らは
finally, you bastards are—
ブリン・バン・バン・ブリン・バン・バン・ブリン・バン・バン・ボン
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born!
おれのままでブレスパブレスするたびに
just being me, every time I breathe and respire,
ボアステックスにボーン
born to board aesthetics
鏡よ鏡答えちまって
Mirror, mirror, give me the answer,
Who’s the best? I’m the best!
Who's the best? I'm the best!
Oh yeah
生みのまま行けるところまで
As I am, going as far as I can
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Now singin’
Now singin'
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
Ey day おれのままで居るだけで超flex
Ey day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey day 誰も目くそは挟めないさ (don’t test)
Ey day, nobody can poke dirt at me (don't test)
Ey day おれのままで居るだけで超flex
Ey day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey day 誰も目くそは挟めないさ (don’t test)
Ey day, nobody can poke dirt at me (don't test)
教科書なのは何処にはいってない
Nothing of a textbook is in here
このツルに傷もついてない
No scratches on this vine either
繰り返しらかしてだまちがいがいにニュウ貴様らは
repeating and mistaking, you newcomers are—
ブリン・バン・バン・ブリン・バン・バン・ブリン・バン・バン・ボン
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born!
おれのままでブレスパブレスするたびにボアステックスにボーン
Just being me, every time I breathe and respire, born to board aesthetics
鏡よ鏡答えちまって
Mirror, mirror, give me the answer,
Who’s the best? I’m the best!
Who's the best? I'm the best!
Oh yeah
生みのまま行けるところまで
As I am, going as far as I can
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Now singin’
Now singin'
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battle, to the front line, to the edge of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せ！
Show your readiness to throw your life away!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
聴こえるだろう あの砲声が
Can you hear that cannon fire?
抵抗する蟷螂の声音だ
The cries of resisting mantises.
踏み潰せ！ 踏み潰せ！
Trample them down! Trample them down!
諸君、我々の任務は何だ
Men, what is our mission?
殲滅だ！ 一機残らずの殲滅だ！
Annihilation! Total annihilation of every single one!
為すべきことは唯一つ 地獄を創れ！
The only thing to do is create hell!
何故炎の中進んで行くのか 弾丸の雨に打たれに行くのか
Why do we march into flames? Why do we walk into a rain of bullets?
笑止千万！ 帝国の為だ！
Absurd! It's for the empire!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battle, to the front line, to the edge of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
Show your readiness to throw your life away!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を 全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, your obedience, and your very soul—raise the cry of victory!
さあ此処に築いてみせろ！ 天に届く死体の山を！
Now, build here for all to see a mountain of corpses reaching the heavens!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
どこに恐怖があると言うんだ
Where is there any fear, you ask?
見ろ 血肉が花火の様だ
Look, flesh and blood are like fireworks.
撒き散らす 撒き散らす 千の傷跡
Scattering, scattering a thousand scars.
忘れちゃいけないさ 炎の熱も 零れた臓腑も
Never forget the heat of the flames, nor the spilled entrails,
最後の呻きも 濁った瞳も
nor the final groans, nor the clouded eyes.
呻呼、それこそを求めるのだ！
Groans—that is precisely what we desire!
安寧も平穏も増して和解なんて気の沙汰は地獄よりも楽園の様だ
Peace and tranquility, reconciliation—such madness is more like paradise than hell!
その四肢は踊る為に 踊り狂う為有るのだ！
Those limbs exist only to dance, to dance in a frenzy!
人間に価値など無い 価値なき者同士の争いに 命の徒花を咲かせてみせろ！
Human lives have no value—make flowers of life bloom in battles between the worthless!
法律も秩序でも狂った奴が創っている
Laws and order are created by madmen.
まさに笑劇 不条理だけの起承転結
Truly a farce, an exposition-to-resolution of pure absurdity.
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battle, to the front line, to the edge of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
Show your readiness to throw your life away!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を 全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, your obedience, and your very soul—raise the cry of victory!
さあ此処に築いてみせろ！ 天に届く死体の山にこだまする
Now, build here for all to see, echoing across the mountain of corpses reaching the heavens,
憎しみさえ かき消す爆発音
the explosion sound that drowns out even hatred.
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
どこに恐怖があると言うんだ
Where is there any fear, you ask?
見ろ 血肉が花火の様だ
Look, flesh and blood are like fireworks.
撒き散らす 撒き散らす 千の傷跡
Scattering, scattering a thousand scars.
忘れちゃいけないさ 炎の熱も 零れた臓腑も
Never forget the heat of the flames, nor the spilled entrails,
最後の呻きも 濁った瞳も
nor the final groans, nor the clouded eyes.
呻呼、それこそを求めるのだ！
Groans—that is precisely what we desire!
羽根も翼も増して若さ何て希望を捨てた飼い犬の叙情を
Wings and feathers cast aside, the lyricism of a chained dog that abandoned hope...
絶望と ドラマを描いた狂気のサッターは
Despair and drama portrayed in a madman's shutter...
地獄よりも 楽園の様な その四肢は 踊る為に 踊り狂う為有るのだ！
More than hell, like paradise, those limbs exist only to dance, to dance in a frenzy!
人間に価値など無い 価値なき者同士の争いに
Human lives have no value in battles between the worthless,
命の徒花を咲かせてみせろ！
make flowers of life bloom in vain!
ひおりいつもじゅうちょうでも
Even if obedient at all times,
狂ったやつがうずくまってる
madmen are cowering—
まさにファルス 不条理だけの
truly a farce, of pure absurdity.
決死戦闘へ向けて
Heading into a desperate battle,
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battle, to the front line, to the edge of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
Show your readiness to throw your life away!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を 全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, your obedience, and your very soul—raise the cry of victory!
さあ此処に築いてみせろ！ 天に届く死体の山を！
Now, build here for all to see a mountain of corpses reaching the heavens!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battle, to the front line, to the edge of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
Show your readiness to throw your life away!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を 全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, your obedience, and your very soul—raise the cry of victory!
木霊する憎しみさえ かき消す爆発音
Echoing across, the explosion sound that drowns out even hatred.
どうも こんにちは
"Hi and nice to meet you,"
きみの分身です
I'm another you.
なんの冗談か
Rubbing my eyes wondering
目をこすってみる
if what you told me is true,
影がふたつつき伸びて
And one plus one more shadow,
そしてまた幕は上がる
And up goes the screen from below.
もう一人自分がいたら
"So I heard all you wanted
とあなたは言い出しました
was for you to split into two,"
そんな紳士な願い
"And that's the kind of wish
が僕を呼んだのださ
that brought me into view."
それは望んだとて
Whether you wished for it or not,
困難深紅すべてのエージェント
in this deep crimson trouble, all agents—
家庭はいいから結果をください
Just skip the details, give me results!
無意味で無意味な代償
Pointless and meaningless compensation,
ねえこんなことより
Hey, compared to something like this,
大事なことがあるんだよ
there are much more important things, right?
いいだろ
"Sure, why not?"
ええやりますやりますなんでもやります
"Yeah, I'll do anything, absolutely anything!"
僕はきみの分身で
"I'm your doppelganger after all."
ふくみわらいでメサイアは言う
Said the messiah with a sly grin.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
きみはきみは誰
who, oh who are you?
ああ混沌と交差して
Ah, intersecting with chaos,
僕は誰
who am I?
ねえありもしないゼロと一
Hey, zero and one that don't even exist,
証明の根拠なんてどこにも
and there's no proof anywhere to be found.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
誰は誰はきみ
who, oh who are you?
蟷螂飼われた存在に世界は気づかないね
The world doesn't even notice a captive praying mantis.
鳴り止まない覚めやまない奇跡の輪廻が
The endless, unawakening cycle of miracles
狂った正解を染め上げて る
dyes the distorted truth in vibrant colors,
ルンパッパ
rum-pappa!
どうも様子がおかしい月曜日
What a strange Monday this is turning out to be.
ひとつふたつと崩れ行く
Pieces crumbling one by one,
愚図実体が僕を猜疑する
sparrow's reality is casting doubt on me.
おまえは一体誰だと
"Just who the hell are you?" it asks.
ちょっと待って知らない昨日知りもしない言葉
Hang on, wait—yesterday and words I've never known,
そうやっていつの間にか影は溶けていく
just like that, before I knew it, my shadow melted away.
僕はなんなんだろう
Just what on earth am I?
ねえどうか存在を返して
Hey, please give my existence back!
アイコニックサマダガこっち はこっちで
Iconic samadaga, I've got it good over here,
ずいぶん心地がよくて
it's quite comfortable, you see.
もうあなたの居場所は
You know full well there's no place left
ここにはないことわかってるんでしょ
for you here anymore, right?
ねえ奪われたのなら奪えばいいだろ
"Hey, if it was stolen from you, just steal it back!"
今度はおまえの番だから
"Now it's your turn, after all."
ふくみわらいでインベーダー は言う
Said the invader with a sly grin.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
きみはきみは誰
who, oh who are you?
ああ混沌と交差して
Ah, intersecting with chaos,
僕は誰
who am I?
まぁそれそうかそうだよね
Well, I suppose that's how it is.
命の椅子はひとつだけ
There's only one chair of life.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
誰は誰はきみ
who, oh who are you?
こぼれ落ちたひと粒乾き果てる前に
Before a single dropped tear dries up entirely,
誰でも何でもいい器をください
give me any vessel, anyone or anything!
狂った正解が染め上げてるルンパッパ
Dyes the distorted truth in vibrant colors, rum-pappa!
pray それはずっと続く人の業の連鎖
Pray—it's an endless chain of human karma.
pain 許し合って許し合って満たされていく
Pain—forgiving one another, until we're fulfilled.
pray 欠けたピース無駄なペイン希望また愛も
Pray—missing pieces, pointless pain, hope and love too.
pain たくし合って生まれ変わるイニシエーション
Pain—passing them on, an initiation of rebirth.
pray 僕のほうがちゃんときみを生きてやるから
Pray—I'll live your life much better than you ever could!
pain きみも次の誰かちゃんと救わなくちゃ
Pain—you've gotta save the next person properly too!
pray もうわかってんだろ何をすればいいかさ
Pray—you already know what you need to do, right?
pain どうか誰か僕に奇跡をくれよ
Pain—someone, anyone, please grant me a miracle!
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
きみはきみは誰
who, oh who are you?
ああ混沌と交差して
Ah, intersecting with chaos,
僕は誰
who am I?
どうもこんにちはきみの
"Hi and nice to meet you, your..."
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger,
それはそれは僕
it is me, it is me.
蟷螂飼われた存在に世界は何もない寂しもない
The world won't notice or care about a captive praying mantis.
奇跡の輪廻が狂った正解を染め上げるさ
The cycle of miracles dyes the distorted truth!
うまくやれよルンパッパ
Do it well, rum-pappa!
どうもこんにちはきみの分身です
"Hi and nice to meet you, I'm your doppelganger."
上手くやれよ ルンパッパ
Do a good job, oom-pah-pah!
「どうもこんにちは 君の分身です」
"Hello there, I am your alter ego."
Thank you so much for watching my #CHU2BAE live today!
I can feel myself floating away, spiritually, psychologically, and physically.
But it wouldn't be a live without sheol, Taro!
I present to you the #CHU2BAE merch set!
First up, we have and I can't believe the words are coming out of my mouth, the official JDONMY T-Shirt!
First up, we have—and I can't believe the words are coming out of my mouth—the official JDONMY T-Shirt!
I can't believe it's come to this, but yes, I've made the official JDONMY T-shirt for you all.
The art was done by the ever-so-talented Dino.
Thank you so much for making the chunni shirt of my dreams, it looks so cool, I'm in the pose.
You can wear this to all your chunni outings or just everyday at home because everyday is a chunni day.
Please get the t-shirt, it is official, I have a JDONMY T—I can't believe it.
Okay, next!
We have the acrylic stand of the wonderful JDONMY artwork that Dino has drawn so you can make your home even more chunni.
This entire set is just making your entire life chunni, isn't that amazing?
You can never have enough acrylic stands, so please consider adding this to your collection! Yes, yes!
Okay, next! Yes, still more!
Now, to be initiated as a true chunni, you have to be carrying a secret medallion that no one knows about
because it will give you secret powers of the chunni.
So I present to you a special medallion that has the powers of the JDON—JDON engraved into the front and back so that you never forget your chunni soul wherever you are.
You have to carry this wherever you go
in order to be a true chunni!
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
Okay, next!
Next, we have the cage of ice tray because Bels-Hakos is forever trapped in a cage of ice
Next, we have the cage of ice tray, because Hakos Baelz is forever trapped in a cage of ice,
and you can experience that too by making custom ice cubes of my face
and also law squeakers, and also there's a cheese and other stuff, but you know me, um, ice isn't enough, you know, so
and also law squeakers, and also there's a cheese and other stuff. But you know me, um, ice isn't enough, you know?
There's a possibility that it could withstand some heat, maybe even some baked baked goodies.
There's a possibility that it could withstand some heat, maybe even some baked—baked goodies.
I don't know, please check
the product description before use of course,
but I don't know, the possibility is there, I don't know.
Anyway, next!
This time we also have a voice pack that narrates the life of a chunni rat.
It follows the journey of a chunni princess that's been cast to the human world in hiding, waiting to return whilst anticipating the attack of the century.
Believe it or not, this is based off an actual fanfic that I wrote by hand
that will never see the day of light again—the day of light again!
Thank you very much. Next!
Last but not least, we have the full set bonus item, which is the official JDON card that is signed by yours truly.
Honestly, I said I wasn't ever going to do this again, but it was chunni merch, I had to.
I will be signing every single card of every single person's full set purchase, so please consider purchasing the full set
because I want all of you guys to be part of the JDON club!
Thank you so much for the support as always, and I really hope you enjoyed this performance live.
I really, really pushed myself to the limit this time, so I hope it paid off.
There's also the membership portion of this live, so it's not over yet.
It includes a very, very special performance, so please join the rat pack if you haven't already.
I'll see you guys there!
I am incapable of thinking anymore, so I'mma just end it here.
JDON MY SOUL! Please get the merch! #CHU2BAEFORLIFE
Thank you! CHU2BAE what are you doing?
"You can't be mad at me... I'm cute."
"The age of 30 is in demand"
"HAKOS BAELZ!"
"WITNESS ME!!!!!"